ininbox.com 2018-02-08

# Privacy Policy | INinbox

**Effective Date: 12/5/2012**

### Where we stand on gathering, sharing and protecting your info

This privacy policy shows our commitment to protecting your info when gathering data from you. It refers specifically to INinbox. This privacy policy describes how INinbox ltd ("INinbox", "We", "Us") collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site [http://www.ininbox.com](http://www.ininbox.com/ "INinbox") and the INinbox Service Platform. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. The use of information collected through our Service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the Service for which our customer has engaged INinbox.

### When you sign up for a free account, we will ask you for information. This information _may include_ :

  * Your name
  * Your company name
  * Your company or home address
  * Your telephone number
  * Your email address
  * Your email list details
  * How many emails you plan to send
  * Whether you use good email marketing practices

### Likewise, when you sign up for a paid plan, we will ask you for the same information as above, as well as:

  * The name on your credit card
  * Your credit card number
  * Your credit card number expiration date
  * The three or four-digit safety code on the back of your card
  * Your billing address

### In addition, if you contact us for more info on any of our partner programs or other programs, we may also ask you:

  * Your DBA organization's name
  * The size of your organization or congregation
  * Your Tax/VAT Number

### What we do with that info

As far as your info goes, excluding your credit card data, here's where we stand:

We may use the information you provide primarily to:

  * Fulfill your registration
  * Send you an email confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis

We do not sell or give your info to any other entity or company.

  * We keep your info strictly for ourselves. 
  * We will not exploit that info.
  * We may use your data for marketing purposes, if only to find out who our customer base is as a whole, or which products you may need in the future, but that's it. We use the strictest standards and protocols to protect your data.
  * When you use your credit card to sign up, we absolutely, 100% protect your data and keep it internal. We use an outside credit card processing company, but they are not permitted to store, retain or use your info except to process your transaction.
  * We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [_customercare@ininbox.com_](mailto:customercare@ininbox.com)

### Your IP address, cookies and other info

When you visit INinbox, we are able to view your IP address. However, **your IP address does not identify you as a user, but merely the general area of where you live.** As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may combine Site Data with other data we have collected from users, such as Customer Registration Data. 

INinbox also uses "cookies" to identify you each time you come back to the site. These cookies also store your data for convenience, including your password and log in name. **Cookies are in no way linked to personally identifiable information.** You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited.

The use of tracking technologies by our service providers, technology partners or other 3rd party assets on the site is not covered by our privacy policy. These 3rd parties may use cookies, clear gifs, images, and scripts to help them better manage their content on our site. We do not have access or control over these technologies. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers' or Users' personally identifiable information.

Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here:

[**http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118**](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118)

### Using our service

When sending emails via our service, we maintain strict privacy for all your data. Hence, **if you upload or create an email list and store it online, and decide to purge or delete those email addresses, we do not keep them on our servers.** They are gone forever, so please take note to export your data before you delete it if you may need to use it in the future.

While we may review your list when you upload it, just to make sure it's opt-in, we do not monitor or review the content beyond that first stage.  
Also, when you create or upload an email list and store it with our service, **we do not sell, rent or give away the data on your list.** That data is yours and yours alone, we merely store it for you when you use our service.

**Regarding 3rd party data processed through our email Service**

INinbox collects information under the direction of our customers, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes as part of providing the Service.

An individual who seeks access, who seeks to correct, amend, delete inaccurate data or withdraw consent to further contact should direct his/her query to the INinbox customer they interact with directly (the data controller). If an Ininbox customer requests that we remove personally identifiable information on their behalf, we will respond to their request within 30 days.

Ininbox will retain personal data we process on behalf of our customers for as long as needed to provide services and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Security

The security of both our customers' and 3rd party individuals' personal data is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [_customercare@ininbox.com_](mailto:customercare@ininbox.com).

### INinbox full disclosure

INinbox will only disclose your data, the content of your private communications, or the contact information of your recipients if required to do so by law, or as otherwise stated in this Statement, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on INinbox; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of INinbox and others, including among other things to enforce our Terms of Service; (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of its members or the public; (4) to correct technical problems and malfunctions in how we provide our service to you and to technically process your information; (5) to take precautions against liability; (6) to respond to claims that information you have submitted to INinbox has violated the rights or interests of a third party; or (7) as permitted by law or to provide information to law enforcement agencies. Also, certain technical processing of e-mail messages and their content that are required for: (1) sending and receiving messages; (2) conform to connecting networks' technical requirements; (3) conform to the limitations of the Service; or (4) other similar technical connecting requirements.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us.

**It is possible that as we continue to develop our business, INinbox may be acquired. In such a transaction, your information may be transferred to the acquiring entity.** Should this happen, you will be notified via email and a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of your personal information. If as a result of the business transition your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, you will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

### What Type of Data Do We Collect?

Generally, we collect or maintain the following categories of data: 

  * **Customer Registration Data** : when a customer, whether an individual or an entity, activates our services, creates an account at the Site or registers at an event we collect account information from that customer. The Customer Registration Data we collect includes individual or contact name, company name, e-mail address, phone number and other contact information, as well as information about services requested and payment information, such as credit card number, expiration date and billing address. We also assign customers a unique username and password to access their account information through the Site;
  * **Customer Message Recipient Data** : we also maintain data that has been provided to us or uploaded to the Site by our customers.  Typically, Customer Message Recipient Data relates to individuals or entities who have opted in to receive email messages or other types of communications from our customers, and may include name, e-mail address, contact information, and other information. Under our Anti-Spam Policy, customers must obtain a recipient's consent prior to sending the recipient an e-mail through our service. For more information, please see the section below entitled "Why Do You Receive E-mails";

Although the majority of our customers are businesses, some of the Customer Registration Data submitted or maintained by us may identify or relate to an individual ("personal data"), rather than a business.  

### User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or deactivate it by making the change on your account settings page or by emailing our Customer Support at [_customercare@ininbox.com_](mailto:customercare@ininbox.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Why Do You Receive Emails?

If you received one or more marketing or promotional e-mails ("commercial e-mails") from us, it means that a) your email address is on our list of customers, trial users or prospective customers; or b) you have provided us your email address so that we could contact you. Each commercial email we send to you contains an unsubscribe link through which you may easily opt-out of receiving future commercial emails from us. If you do not wish to receive additional commercial emails from INinbox, simply click the unsubscribe link and follow the instructions to unsubscribe your e-mail address or to change your preferences about the types of e-mail we send you. If you believe you received an email from us in error, please contact us immediately at _abuse@ininbox.com_

Our customers may also use INinbox's service to send commercial e-mails to users who have opted-in to receive such e-mails. According to INinbox's Anti-Spam Policy, our customers are not permitted to send unsolicited marketing or promotional e-mails, and are required to obtain opt-in consent from a recipient, prior to sending a commercial e-mail to the recipient's e-mail address. 

While we have a strict Anti-Spam Policy, we can not guarantee that our customers will always honor such policy. If you believe you have received an e-mail from one of our customers in error or in violation of our Anti-Spam Policy, please contact us immediately at _abuse@ininbox.com_

### _Newsletters_

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each newsletter or by emailing us at [customercare@ininbox.com](mailto:customercare@ininbox.com).

If you have unsubscribed but continue to receive e-mail from us or from one of our customers, you may report this to _abuse@ininbox.com_. Please note that unsubscribe requests may take up to 7 - 10 days to process.

**3rd Party Sites and Assets**

INinbox's web site, or messages created with INinbox, may contain links to other Websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of INinbox. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. INinbox is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and other Widgets, such as the Share this button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

As described above, third parties may independently collect information about you when you view ads or other communications from third parties through INinbox products or services. **If you do not want those companies to collect information about you, please contact them directly.**

### INinbox policy changes

As with any business, we reserve the right to make changes to our privacy statement, polices and practices. Should this happen, we will notify you at least 30 days before those changes take place (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. If these new policies and practices reflect something different than what we're already doing, we'll give you the choice, at least 30 days in advance of those changes, to either continue with us or cancel your service and go elsewhere.

### Contact Us

US +1 315 217 4268

Erasmuslaan 16  
9752 PG Haren  
The Netherlands
